Here we go.
All right, all right, all right.
Did you miss me?
William Radford.
Okay.
♪ Introspection,
doubtful thoughts ♪
♪ They weaken men ♪
♪ While the tyrants
manipulate and poison them ♪
♪ Fatal attraction,
desire's such a fickle thing ♪
Hmm.
♪ No satisfaction
if you let yourself give in ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ Keep your head up... ♪
You ran out
of the house this morning,
but I need you to get the kids
to school.
♪ We're all kings
and queens within ♪
♪ Keep your head up... ♪
My battery's dying.
I'm sure I'm being spied on.
Shut up, man.
You're just paranoid.
♪ A great disaster ♪
♪ Distracts from boredom
ahead ♪
♪ Fire and brimstone ♪
♪ A warning of nothing
for men ♪
♪ Are you complicit? ♪
♪ Or will you be there
to defend? ♪
♪ Legitimize the lack
of empathy within ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ If you want to do
your thing... ♪
Good morning. What's up?
Look. Take a look at this.
Any noise about it on your end?
No.
I watch people, not weather.
I've never seen
global storms like this.
We can't figure out
what's causing
this atmospheric phenomena.
Something is way off.
Their size, the amount...
All of it,
it just doesn't...
doesn't make sense.
All right,
that's crazy right there.
All of NASA's
satellites are blind.
We haven't been able to see
anything for two days.
Can't figure it out.
Yeah.
Well, I got bigger fish to fry
than watching clouds.
Look, duty calls,
so just keep me posted.
- Not on my watch.
- Everywhere we go,
everything we say,
watch, read, and write
is captured and evaluated to
censor our awareness of the truth
and to enslave us
to tyrannical, authoritarian
government control.
Okay, Guardian.
The surveillance state has also
not revealed that
the Goliath program
is an existential threat
to humanity
that no one can
possibly comprehend.
You will see all the alarming
details in full disclosure
in the Goliath documents
that I'm releasing to the world.
All right, now let's
go to suspect number two.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- A muffin?
Really? A muffin?
What are you thinking?
Jesus, Dad. How many times
have we been through this?
One hard-boiled egg.
All right? They're right next
to the doughnuts.
Would it kill you?
- You need more protein.
- I need to get to work.
No, you need to lay off
the soy milk.
You haven't had any protein
this week.
- How do you know?
- Let's just say me and your fridge is pretty tight.
You hacked my fridge?
- Dad.
- Lay off of that stuff.
It's no good for the baby.
- It has zero calcium.
- Uh, it does have calcium.
I majored in bio, remember?
Hold on.
Just what I've been waiting for.
You little punk, I got you.
I see you took the
Sunday graveyard shift again.
When's the last time
you left the office?
- That's classified.
- You need to get some sun.
I don't know what looks worse,
you or your poor plant over there.
- Dad?
- I just... got to focus
on this right here real quick.
Um, I, uh, got to get back
to the lab and finish up
my project.
All right, I love you.
Yo. Did you delete my game?
You know you're wasting
your time with that game.
Dad, playing video games
is my job.
I'm a tech visionary
in a pre-funding stage.
A tech to who the what?
All I know is I've been
pre-funding your ass for years
and you need to get a real job.
This is my job.
Look, son, I got a friend
over at NSA.
- They're recruiting next month.
- Let it go.
I mean, spying on what's
in people's Amazon carts?
Is that what you think I do?
- I'm sorry, did you get promoted?
- Listen, smart-ass.
I know people would rather have
someone watch them...
- Really? That's the choice?
- than blow them up.
Give up our privacy or death?
Yep. I think it's a pretty
fair trade, if you ask me.
Well, I respectfully disagree.
Respect? I don't see no respect.
All I see is a kid
with a $200,000 education
living in my damn house, playing
dumb-ass video games. That's what I see.
You mean Mom's house.
What'd you say?
Come on,
you haven't even cleaned out
her stuff yet.
That's none of
your damn business.
Saved by the bell.
If anyone
should be gaming, it's you.
- Might be good therapy for all that aggression.
- I'll call you later.
You mine.
You are officially found.
- Bam!
- That was easy.
Nah, I'm just good.
Let's get my eye in the sky.
Good morning,
my sweet baby drone.
Lord have mercy.
There's no James at all?
- Yes, Mark, what is it?
- Hey, Pops.
"Pops"? I'm not your daddy, man.
Right. Uh... Sorry.
- "Sorry" what?
- Sorry, sir.
Um, anyway,
I know you told Faith
you have to work,
but just to tempt you,
we're all wearing
these fun shirts to the shower.
I, uh, even got
a Grandpa Shark one for you.
Look.
He's grumpy, too.
He's got your whiskers
and everything.
- What shower?
- Oh, shit.
Sorry, uh, I guess
I should've talked to Faith
before I made shirts. My bad.
Keep up the good work
over there, okay?
Uh, and thank-thank you
for your service.
Damn.
Changed her password again.
Oh, shit.
What an asshole.
Remember
to take out the trash today
and be nice to the kids.
I love you, baby.
Yeah.
- Boom!
- That was easy.
Say it again.
That was easy.
Damn right.
William. You really took your
time with this one, didn't you?
Oh, shit. Hold on, hold on. I got
to add Briggs to this conversation.
All right.
Director Briggs, you have
FBI Special Agent Jeffries
- on the line.
- Sir.
Good to meet you, Jeffries.
- Cams are hot.
- All right. Ready here.
Body cam check.
All coming in clear.
- Will, what's the unit number?
- Checking. Stand by.
Listen up, team.
I want this to be clean
and surgical.
We don't know
who these hackers are,
but we know
what they're capable of.
This so-called Disruptor
is trying to reveal
a top secret program
called Goliath,
and that file must not go out.
It's national security.
Don't worry, sir.
We're all over this guy.
You little punk.
Touchdown.
Uh, second floor,
east corner, unit 42.
Copy that. Moving in.
All right. Going up the stairs.
All right, second
floor is clear to proceed.
Ooh!
Guys, you need to hurry.
These security cameras
are on public networks.
Disruptor could be watching
our every move.
Copy that.
Open door, unit 209.
Back inside. Lock the door.
Approaching.
Here we go.
Oh, shit.
It's another one of his decoys.
Clever little bastard.
Shit.
What the hell was that?
Jesus, what the hell was that?
Will, what was that?
I'm checking. Stand by.
Shit.
Uh, reports are pouring in...
- Oh, this is insane.
- falling debris or meteors,
but we can't tell yet
what exactly is going on.
It's pandemonium.
Uh, reports coming in:
Fires in Dodger Stadium.
- Shit.
- Uh, a Century City
building has collapsed.
supposed to break up
and burn up
upon entering
Earth's atmosphere,
becoming what used to be
called shooting stars.
Oh.
Jesus.
Oh!
Some are speeding up.
Some are slowing down.
This scatters their entry points
across the hemisphere,
maybe even wider.
Your location is gonna get hit.
I'm heading to one
of the crash sites now.
Shit!
Whoa!
Come on, come on. Pick up.
Come on. Where are you?
Got you.
Okay. Just sit tight, baby.
FEMA has instructed
all citizens
to take shelter immediately
on the ground.
Basements, parking garages,
fallout shelters,
anything that can provide
safe and effective coverage
until the meteor storm
has stopped.
We have no other information
at this point,
but world government leaders
are engaging to determine
the amount of damage
- and casualties so far.
- Come on! Come on!
Hey, Dad.
Dad, Dad, you seeing this?
- Are you seeing this? Oh, my...
- Dave.
Listen to me.
Get out of there now.
Dave!
No, no, no! You got to get up!
Keep running!
What? I can't hear you.
You got to go left now!
- And run, boy!
- Dad, Dad.
Make a right now at the corner!
- Holy shit.
- Dave!
- I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Go.
Go!
Come on, come on. Come on, Dave.
Come on.
Thank God.
President is safe,
location undisclosed.
VP, justices, chiefs of staff
all secure.
Okay. We have DHS joining,
and we have NASA on the ground
at an event site.
Dr. Salas,
what do you see in there?
Wow.
Whoa.
Oh, my God.
This is incredible.
I'm gonna get closer.
It's huge. It's got to be
like 30, 40 feet.
With this size and shape,
they should've shattered.
Can you tell yet
what they're comprised of?
No, sir, I've never seen
anything like this.
Whoa!
- What was that?
- Stand by.
What the hell was that?
Stand by.
I'm rerouting her cell
to our satellite.
Wow. This is incredible.
It's, uh... it's freezing cold.
It's, um...
Oh, my God!
- Get away!
- Oh, my God!
What the hell is that?
Sandra!
Sa...
Secretary Crystal, the protocol
is DEFCON here, yes?
Absolutely.
Authorizing DEFCON now.
I'll notify the president.
Prioritize all armed assets
to domestic meteor sites
immediately.
We need to contain
whatever the hell that was.
I'm talking
full mobilization here.
We're on it.
Come on, come on, come on.
General Austin,
if this is happening worldwide,
we'll need to sync up
immediately to coordinate intel.
Reach out to the UN,
NATO, everyone.
Nothing short
of a planetary alliance.
I'm calling
for an urgent meeting
with the UN General Assembly
right now.
Crystal,
once the president is secure,
brief him on what you saw.
He's gonna need
to make a statement,
declare a state of emergency.
Absolutely.
Will, you're
my eyes and ears on this.
I need your domestic threat
analysis right away.
Roger that.
Radford. What are the rules
of engagement here?
Engagement? Shit if I know.
Don't do nothing.
What the hell is that?
That thing is huge.
Whoa.
Can't believe this shit.
Goddamn.
Oh, my God.
What the hell is that, Will?
Oh... my... God.
Sit tight.
I'm coming back to you.
- How you doing? You all right?
- I figured this would be a safe place to talk.
Listen, I need you to get
to your sister right now.
Nah, Dad, Dad,
I-I spoke to her. She's safe.
Mark's picking her up.
Listen, I need to talk to you
about something I stumbled on.
I don't have time
for that right now, okay?
Dad! This is important.
I don't think you understand
the dynamics at play here.
Nobody understands, okay?
We're in a national crisis here.
Goddamn it, Dad, I do.
I have information
I think you might want to know.
Not now, Dave. Not now.
I need you to stay sheltered
and sit tight.
- Will.
- I'm here.
They're not doing anything.
This doesn't feel right.
Just hold tight,
hold tight, hold tight.
Oh!
Oh. Run!
Get out of there!
No! No!
Sheila!
Oh, my God.
Uh,
eyewitness video is coming in
from all over the world
of terrifying machines
rising out of these meteors.
Citizens are astonished
by what is happening.
Destruction and chaos
is rampant worldwide.
Now, as far as we know,
governments
have not yet determined
what these things are and
what their response will be.
Damn.
Space Force, NASA,
and the UAP Task Force
are headed to event sites
right now.
We've been instructed
to announce
that people of the world
should shelter in place.
Absolutely do not go outside.
Destruction is widespread
as these machines make their way
through cities,
towns and rural areas,
annihilating
critical infrastructure,
resources, military bases
and communication centers
across the world.
We've been told from Space Force
that the violent storms
around the world
were caused by the massive
atmospheric disruption...
from thousands of meteors
burning through
the Earth's ozone
at the same time.
This attack was
clearly organized...
and coordinated
by an intelligent force,
and the storm should have been
an immediate emergency,
but all satellites
were blinded...
and no one on Earth
could see what was coming.
We'll have more information
on satellites soon.
Mark never showed, Dad.
What are you doing outside?
Dad.
Get away from that! Okay?
Stay clear of that stuff!
Hey! Hey! Get out of there!
Go!
Run!
Go! Faith!
Oh, shit! Shit!
- Dad! Dad!
- Faith!
Faith.
Faith!
Are you okay?
Come on. Okay.
Look.
How... how are you?
How's the baby?
Oh, my God, it hurts so bad.
Okay, stay calm.
Stay calm.
Your heart rate is way too high.
Don't you move, okay?
All operators are busy now.
Please try
your call another time.
I'm coming!
I'm coming for you now!
Okay?
Here I come!
Damn it! We're in lockdown.
Access denied.
Damn it.
- Okay.
- Access granted.
Okay.
Okay, I'm coming.
I'm coming right now.
Okay. I'm coming to you.
- I'm coming to you.
- Dad.
Okay.
I got to take the steps.
- What happened?
- Has to be DEFCON 1.
All essential buildings secured.
The irony, right, Dad?
Access denied.
Come on! Come on!
Son of a bitch!
You never want to
leave that place.
And
now it won't let you leave.
Don't worry.
I'm gonna figure something out,
honey.
I'm gonna figure something out.
I'm sorry, but I'm coming.
- Dad, it hurts so bad.
- Okay, okay.
Stay calm. Stay calm.
I got to get to shelter.
My office is only a mile away.
- I can make it.
- No. No.
Stay where you are.
I'm-a get you out of there.
Dad, what's that sound?
Shit! It's close by.
Look, I'm getting you
out of there. Just hold tight.
You see that Tesla
in front of you?
- I need you to get to it.
- Dad, I can't drive like this.
Don't worry. I got you.
Quick as you can.
I'll open it for you.
Hurry up, baby. Come on, Faith.
Hurry, hurry.
A little faster, honey.
I know it hurts.
Okay, I'm getting you out
of there right now. Hold tight.
Man, that was close.
Faith. Listen to me. I got you.
- I got you.
- Okay.
All right.
Hospitals are full, baby,
but don't worry.
I'm gonna get you
to a secure location.
Your destination
- is one mile away.
- Oh, my God.
There's so much destruction.
Don't look at that, sweetheart.
Just keep your eyes on me.
Just focus on me.
Okay.
All right, I got you.
I got everything under control.
Hey.
I don't blame you for not
wanting me at your shower.
Now? We have to do this now?
No.
I'm serious. I mean...
I put you and your brother
through a lot of pain.
Jesus, Dad.
Do you know
what your problem is?
You think you have more power
than you really do.
You think you had the power to
have saved Mom from a disease.
You think you have
the power to make me happy.
You think you have the power
to keep the world safe.
You got to wake up.
You don't have any power.
None.
You got to let go.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Okay.
All right.
Turn right.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on.
- Mark, Mark, can you hear me?
- What?
- Mark.
- Who is that?
It's me, Will.
Faith is in trouble.
What?
- She's injured.
- No, uh, uh, sh...
My-my phone's been frizzing
out. I-I'm on my way to her now.
Mark, you listen closely.
Faith is losing blood.
Now, you get your skinny ass
over there now.
I'm on my way to her right now.
Oh, thank God.
Wait. What?
A delayed report just came in
from the International
Space Station,
confirming the violent storms
the world experienced
were from thousands of meteors
blasting through the atmosphere.
Meteors were
intentionally crashed
into hundreds of satellites...
to obliterate
any chance of a warning.
Also, military assets worldwide
are assembled to strike back.
We're told the U.S. president
is being briefed any minute now.
Attack squadrons of F-35s
and Black Hawks are on standby
to launch hundreds of sorties
while AWACS are taking off now
to identify priority
strike targets.
Chinooks and C-130s are
dropping airborne troops to engage
once the presidential order
has been given.
Ground troops are making
their way to the front lines.
Tank battalions
are positioning in cities
while the Norfolk naval fleet
is closing in.
They have wiped out
our entire satellite network,
and we have no intel
on our sensitive locations.
I had DHS
terror analyst Will Radford
prepare the threat report.
Will, what are
the high-priority,
most vulnerable sites?
Mr. President, gentlemen,
we're seeing a full attack
on our infrastructure:
On power grids, water,
communication
and top-level military targets.
They knew exactly
where they were going,
and they are systematically
eliminating resources
and our ability
to coordinate a response.
Here, let me show you.
These locations are our
global response headquarters,
our most sensitive targets,
and they're taking them out
one by one.
Based on their
prioritized destruction
of these critical
intelligence command centers,
my analysis suggests
nuclear power facilities
are next.
Electric grids will follow,
leaving us completely helpless.
Do you see that?
They're grouping
to concentrate their attack.
Exactly.
And they will be
much stronger in groups,
so if we concentrate
our armed response assets
to our high-priority locations,
we can hit as many as possible.
I think it's the only option
we have right now.
Our forces are positioned
and ready to engage right now.
What do you think,
Mr. President?
This plan is
humanity's last stand.
I see no other option
but to initiate
this war of the worlds
to save us all.
NATO, China, and the U.S.
have joined forces in what is
an unprecedented collaboration
to defend our cities,
our countries, our way of life.
The world's governments
have finally
put aside their differences
in an effort to protect
the home planet.
CNN reporting
a breaking live update.
The United States president
is calling
the global military response
a "war of the worlds"
- to save humanity.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
Air, sea and land forces
have been activated worldwide
to confront these invaders
directly.
Victories and defeats
are unpredictable...
- That's a lot.
- but casualties are certain.
Got him! Got him!
Whoo! Hell yeah.
No one knows
if our weapons will be able
to deter their advancement,
but global forces are unloading
everything they have right now.
Took your ass out, huh?
These guys threaten
our way of life,
we're gonna take the battle
right to 'em.
Take your intergalactic asses
back home.
Back home!
As the global joint
military operation continues,
this reporter can't help
but wonder, why are they here?
- The hell do they want?
- It is unclear how long it'll take
the world's forces to stop
the rampage of the invaders
against critical
human resources.
D.C. has publicly stated
that they will not speculate
why they attacked
and what they could want.
The attack is a total mystery.
- All we know at this time...
- Whoa.
is that these machines
are making their way
to what appears to be
predetermined destinations.
They are clearly coordinated
and seem to have a plan.
So far, nothing is able
to stop their advance,
and the military
counteroffensive
is continuing to bombard
their relentless procession.
Dad, I got to get this thing
out of my leg.
No, no, no, no. Don't touch it.
Wait for Mark.
Hold on, honey.
Just hold tight.
I'll check on Mark.
Do not touch that thing.
Just relax.
Oh, it hurts so bad.
Don't hang up, Faith.
Mark, hurry up!
- I'm almost there, Pops.
- You better be.
You call me
soon as you get there, okay?
I will, I will.
Oh, I'm cramping up.
Okay, he's almost there, honey.
You sit tight.
I'll come back to you.
Just holler if you need me.
I'll be right here, sweetheart.
Look.
It just stopped.
It's changing directions.
It's hunting for something,
Will.
What's that sound?
What the hell is that?
Every time they make that sound,
they change directions.
They're not trying
to communicate.
They're trying to locate.
What are you looking for?
What are they doing?
Now, what the hell
is that thing?
All right,
just-just hear me out on this.
- The government...
- No, no, no, no.
I don't want to hear nothing
you have to say
that starts off
with "the government."
The government's been keeping
secrets from you, Dad.
From all of us.
They have a surveillance
network that-that's
a thousand times stronger
than anything you could imagine.
You don't think I know about the
government surveillance network?
I am the government
surveillance network.
You don't know about this one!
- But you do?
- Yes.
- It's called Goliath.
- That's fake news.
Think about it.
What do you think all these
private space launch firms
are doing?
All these secret satellites
they're launching?
That's Goliath?
Some secret satellites?
Yes, yes.
Wirelessly transmitted
to some underground facility
on the East Coast.
Jesus, Dave.
Dad, Dad, listen!
Goliath collects
everything on us,
and it won't stop
until they have it all.
Son, I love you,
but you got to leave this
conspiracy shit at the door.
I got to go.
Will, check this out.
Stay indoors.
Keep away from windows.
It looks like
a missile took it down.
But it's still alive.
I can hear it.
That's One Wilshire.
Stay indoors.
You know,
everywhere they've been going,
- there's a data center.
- Data center?
Yeah. They found
all the government servers.
Look, I need you to get closer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Hang on.
Take shelter.
Stay indoors.
There, there. What's that?
Hold on. What is this thing?
What... This thing
looks alive, too.
It looks like it smashed
its way into the building.
- I'm going in.
- Okay. Be careful.
Reports are coming
in that the machines' destinations
appear to be top secret
government data centers.
Damn.
My feeds are down.
Can you get me
eyes on that thing?
Tripods around the globe
have encircled these facilities,
but no one understands
why or what
could be attracting them
to these locations.
What the hell is that stuff?
Something's going on
with the servers.
What in the world?
Will, th-this thing
is branched out everywhere,
and it's-it's covering
the servers.
Oh, shit.
They're in hyper download.
They're being emptied.
Emptied?
These are amazing.
Sandra, get out of there.
Oh, my God!
- They're all over me!
- Sandra!
They're in my clothes.
Sandra.
Oh, shit.
Come on, pick up.
Pick up.
Shit.
Target acquired.
Missile locked.
Shit! Abort, abort, abort!
Oh, no.
The Pentagon
has issued a dire report.
The global military forces
are experiencing
a complete cyberattack.
Strategic Command
is not able to communicate
with any forces, and the world's
counteroffensive is crumbling
as we report this to you now.
All systems have been
penetrated and data-drained.
We must result to a full
manual attack at this point.
There are no other options.
The world's military
has been completely crippled.
Every system
has been penetrated
and drained of data.
Casualties are mounting
at a furious pace,
and entire battalions
are retreating everywhere.
The military are sitting ducks
and being slaughtered without
their advanced digital systems
and now engaging these invaders
in what amounts to be
hand-to-hand combat
just to get our troops
out of immediate harm's way
before being
completely annihilated.
reach you.
There's a problem.
Oh, so you made it?
What's going on?
Yeah, I'm-I'm with her,
but she's...
- Sweetie.
- I thought that I could
stop the bleeding
if I took it out.
Mark. Mark!
You need to do something.
- Do what?
- Something!
What can I do?
To stop the bleeding,
you got to put some pressure
- on that wound, man.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay.
- No.
Mark, no.
You got to get
something else, man.
- You need a tourniquet.
- Trust me.
I'm a pro.
That's not gonna work.
Dad, Dad, just...
have some faith.
All right, it worked.
Bleeding stopped.
- Are you okay?
- Mark.
Keep me posted.
You got it, Pops.
Evacuations are now
all that the world can do
to protect itself.
Okay, so you made it.
Good, good.
- What's going on?
- My new pets.
Look. They even do tricks.
Hmm.
Why are they going
after the chip?
The same reason
they love my phone.
These little guys
are drawn to data.
- What do you mean "drawn to data"?
- It's intelligent.
The more data it consumes,
the smarter it gets.
These things eat data?
Exactly.
That's why those servers
were being emptied.
Wait a minute.
Holy shit.
This whole attack
is just a big diversion
to get those Tripods
to the data centers.
And those Tripods
are just Trojan horses
to get those little bugs
into the servers.
To get to the data.
Hey, I'll circle back.
Tanker ships
around the globe are frozen
without any GPS data,
and oil rigs are com busting.
This is terrible.
Commercial airlines
are grounded by the FAA,
but those still in the air
have no way to navigate
as their on board systems
have failed.
Nuclear power facilities
are paralyzed
and are not able
to generate electricity.
With traffic
escaping cities in gridlock,
there's no way to get away
from the invasion.
Power grids are collapsing
in mass numbers.
The world is going dark
as we speak.
Financial data has been
completely drained and erased,
making the Earth's population
- totally bankrupt.
- My God.
Reports from around the world
show mass rioting
and looting
to get whatever they can.
We are in utter chaos
without our most precious
resource: Our data.
Shit!
No. No, no, no. No, no!
Remember
to take out the trash today
and be nice to the kids.
I love you, baby.
Remember
to take out the trash today
and be nice to the kids.
Fuck!
It's too late now.
It won't stop
until they have it all.
- It won't stop until they have it all.
- Whoa.
It won't stop
until they have it all.
It won't
stop until they have it all.
It won't stop
until they have it all.
It's you?!
- It's you.
- Yeah.
Well, yes, kind of. I...
- How could you, man?
- Yeah.
How could you?
My own son is hacking
the government.
You know, for someone who spends their
life watching, you sure do miss a lot.
Look, the past is the past.
I'm ready to work together now.
Are you?
I got to go.
All you see is broken glass.
Businesses are all closed,
and the people need supplies.
It's dog-eat-dog out here.
Oh, my God.
What is this?
"Violent weather,"
"strange craft sightings."
What the hell are those things?
Collecting data? Ah, man.
That's what brought them here
in the first place.
They knew.
They knew,
and they hid it from us.
They hid it from everybody.
They even knew
about these things.
Goliath. Damn.
Dave was right.
They lied to me the whole time.
Right to my face.
Holy shit.
Briggs is behind
the whole thing.
No wonder he wanted
to catch the Disruptor.
It's too
risky, Briggs. Shut it down now.
With all due respect, General,
Goliath will be activated
whether you like it or not.
It's the greatest
surveillance system
- the world has ever seen.
- They will come for it.
It'll be a full invasion,
damn it.
Invasion?
We now have the ability
to predict every person's
thoughts and movements.
It's total control.
So Briggs went rogue,
put the whole damn thing
in this building
right under my feet?
You crazy bastard.
You can't act alone on this,
Briggs.
Oh, really? Watch me, General.
Yeah, I know all about Goliath.
Wow. You did it.
I can always spot talent.
NASA warned you,
if you activated Goliath,
it could spark an invasion.
Those dinosaur bureaucrats
don't keep us safe. I do!
When you turned on Goliath,
you rang a dinner bell
that traveled throughout
the whole galaxy.
Don't worry,
they won't get into Goliath.
I air-gapped the entire system.
We're safe. I kept us safe.
You risked all of our lives just
to spy on people's Amazon carts!
Come on, Radford.
The government's
like mommy and daddy.
If we can't track our babies,
how can we protect them?
Is that what this is about?
Well, my family's not protected.
They're not safe.
DHS building is
a goddamn bunker.
Goliath is 40 feet underground.
There's no way
they can get to it.
- I made sure of it.
- You're insane.
I didn't sign up for this shit.
No way, ho how.
Well, then, thank you
for your service, Radford.
- You're dismissed.
- Got to stop this thing. Wait!
Come on. No, no, no, no.
Shit.
Damn it.
Oh, no.
You clever little shit.
Love you, boy.
Touchdown.
Touchdown! Touchdown!
Kiss my ass, Briggs.
How you like me now?
William Radford.
Good.
Thank God.
Okay. So what do we do?
All right.
What if we starve them out?
Take away the data, flood
the servers until they crash.
You mean
a denial-of-service attack?
- Exactly.
- Nah.
A D-DoS won't cut it.
We got to poison
they food supply, okay?
So we got to infect
all the data centers.
Come with a good old-fashioned
rabbit virus.
Yo, that's what I'm talking
about. Dad, that-that's classic.
We got to go old-school. The
bigger they are, the harder they fall.
- Exactly.
- Now, one thing I know:
No way, no how can you and I
write this virus alone.
Well, not alone,
but if we had the right team.
Okay. I'll make some calls.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Just, everyone you know sucks.
I'll make the calls.
All right, Disruptor.
Let's disrupt some shit.
Dad, meet my Disruptors.
Your dad's DHS.
He's the goddamn enemy.
What the hell?
You turn on us, Dave?
- Lord have mercy.
- I thought this was
supposed to be our safe space.
Guys, guys, enough.
These aliens are here
for one reason: Goliath.
We thought shit was bad now,
once they get access to it, it's over.
So, what do you want to do?
We use the data centers
they've connected to as bait
and plant an old-school
rabbit virus
to infect the data
they're eating.
My dad's DHS connections
will get us in.
But we must get the rabbit
virus payload uploaded.
Your dad's
got to give us total immunity.
All right, fellas.
That's a deal.
And... your records are wiped.
I'll create the rabbit virus.
Starfire, brute-force passwords.
Thelma & Louise,
break encryption.
Code Crusher, bypass firewalls.
And, Burnout,
just stay out of trouble.
I'll steal the SSL keys
and start hijacking
user credentials.
All right, let's go.
Just whipping up
a little something-something.
Okay.
This is the last time
you ever spy on someone again,
Briggs.
It's too
risky, Briggs. Shut it down now.
With all due respect, General,
Goliath will be activated
whether you like it or not.
It's the greatest
surveillance system
- the world has ever seen.
- They will come for it.
It'll be a full invasion,
damn it.
Invasion? Give me a break.
We now have the ability
to predict every person's
thoughts and movements.
Our most
precious resource on Earth
is food for the superior
intelligence that invaded Earth.
The government knew
this would happen,
and they activated Goliath
anyway.
Holy shit, Dad.
Your dad's OG.
Damn, Mr. Radford,
that was badass.
How you like me now?
Man, I can't believe
I just did that.
Congratulations, Dad.
You're officially a Disruptor.
Welcome to the crew.
All right,
we got the rabbit virus.
Sending it to you now.
Bombs away.
All right,
the virus is launched.
Here we go, here we go.
Been waiting to take
down the government for years.
Eat it up.
Yeah, eat it.
Damn it.
Something's wrong.
I'm being hacked.
They're hacking us!
They're eating our data.
My data's being drained!
They're gonna
find Goliath with it.
Are you serious?
Look at this.
You're freaking
breaking up, man.
Oh, my God!
Shit, shit, shit.
Shit!
The Capitol
is under full attack!
You guys are totally exposed.
They got your IPs.
Y'all got to get out of there.
- Haul ass now!
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Shit.
Hey! Get out of there!
Starfire!
Hey.
It's near our house.
No, no, that...
Dave, get out of there now!
Dave, it's out... No!
Dave!
No!
He's okay. He's okay. He's okay.
No.
He's okay, he's okay. He's okay.
Reports are flooding
in of massive destruction
that has just occurred
at several global locations.
We're hearing that
these machines have separated
from their legs and are
attacking specific targets.
He's okay. He's okay.
We don't know how
many casualties have been incurred,
but the destruction
is said to be absolute
and that no one
could have survived.
Emergency services
are overwhelmed and are unable
to provide any rescue personnel
at this time.
Okay, okay.
Dave?
Son, is-is that you?
What is this?
That was freaking intense.
My God, man!
I...
I thought you got hurt.
I-I thought...
I thought you was in the house.
- Oh, you thought I was home.
- This is crazy.
Nah, I bounced my signal.
I'm chilling at Brian's house.
You had me
worried to death, man.
Why do you think you couldn't
find Disruptor for a year?
Yeah, but...
- but they blew up my house.
- Uh-huh.
They blew up my house, man.
- I...
- Dad, Dad, let's focus.
Why couldn't you run that signal
through Brian's house
- so they can blow his shit up, huh?
- Look, Dad.
We got a lot
of work to do, so...
I don't have
alien invasion insurance.
I'll circle back.
Hey, I have to
show you something.
It looks like plastic,
metal, and silicon.
Right, like everything you'd
expect to see on a microchip.
But look here.
Shit.
Why is there blood
inside of a computer chip?
They're a hybrid organism:
Biological and cyber.
- I mean, look, there's even DNA.
- DNA?
- Oh, my God.
- Life and computers becoming one.
Hold tight. Hold tight.
Faith, do you have access
to your cannibal code?
You know about that?
These things are alive.
- That means we can kill 'em.
- It's never been tested.
They're a hybrid organism:
Biological and cyber.
That explains why a computer
virus couldn't stop 'em.
- Exactly.
- DNA's a lot like computer code.
Why can't you just reprogram
the DNA in the aliens
to cannibalize themselves?
Mark, that's absolutely right.
- We-we can rewrite Faith's code.
- Okay.
Here's what we do:
We upload it to Goliath.
How would we get it
into Goliath?
I'll worry about that.
Dave, Faith,
you guys just work on that code
and get it to me.
Okay, I'll send Dave
the DNA sequence
so he can translate it
into code.
Hmm. We'll see about that.
The Goliath server
complex is deep underground at DHS.
We must collapse
the DHS building on top of it.
A 40-foot pile of rubble on top
won't allow them to get to it.
We're out of time.
We must bomb D.C.
to stop their advance.
We must destroy DHS to make sure
anything that gets through
can't get to Goliath.
No!
Military has POTUS's authority
to combat this threat
with any means necessary.
Our estimated blast radius
for the D.C. area
is five miles.
We've already begun
immediate evacuations...
- Hell no.
- although casualties will be very high.
I've initiated lockdown of
our most sensitive
government buildings
in preparation
for the incoming bombing.
DHS is to be hit twice
and twice as hard
to ensure total destruction.
We're out of time.
They're gonna bomb D.C. and DHS.
We got to get that
cannibal code in 'em fast.
Dad, you're gonna
have to get the code
- into the servers manually.
- Exactly.
No, the code
you will be carrying is data.
They're gonna devour you
along with it.
- I'll be fine.
- Dad.
- They will kill you, Will.
- I'll be fine.
It's a damn suicide mission.
I said I'll be fine.
We're out of options.
All right, the code is ready.
Sending it to you now.
Put it on a thumb drive.
I don't have a thumb drive.
What do you mean
you don't have a thumb drive?
Even I have a thumb drive.
Boy, this is a top secret
military installation.
They don't let thumb drives
in the building.
Um, Faith can load it here
and I can get it to you.
How?
Prime Air.
Prime Air?
Oh, it's, uh...
it's the future of delivery.
They've been training us
for months.
I need you to place
an official order on Amazon
- to activate the drone.
- This is nuts.
We only got one shot at this.
Are you sure
you can get it here?
Don't worry. I fly like a bird.
I can soar like an eagle
with this thing.
Okay, Mark. I believe in you.
Will, are you seeing this?
Shit.
B-2 stealth bombers
are taking off
from Langley, Virginia
Air Force Base
and are estimated to strike
D.C. targets in ten minutes.
You got to move fast.
Now, Faith, I'm sending you
the blueprints to DHS.
You're gonna guide me
down to Goliath.
Okay, Dad.
I'm giving you all
full access to my system.
Sandra, I need you to be
my eyes and my ears.
- Copy that.
- Let me know what's going on at all times.
Okay. I'm out.
Hey, Mark.
Protect that sweet baby drone.
You got it, Pops.
How we looking?
Oh, shit.
Washington, D.C.
is being destroyed.
All machines seem to be headed
towards the DHS complex.
Will, they're headed
right your way.
Sandra,
where are those bombers?
Hang on. Stand by.
About eight minutes out.
DHS is the last target.
- Hit it hard.
- Roger that.
Initiating target lock on DHS
and surrounding threats.
I'm heading out!
Incoming!
Guys, I need some cover here.
Faith, get me an access
code to a Reaper drone now.
Dad, how do I get that?
Right click on the map.
Select "show active drones."
- Roger that.
- Guys, I need some cover here!
- I got a bogey on my tail!
- Okay, Dave.
I'm sending you
the closest one now.
Give me one second.
- Oh, shit. Shit.
- You got to hurry, Dave.
Just a few more seconds.
This thing's on my tail.
A little help here, please.
Don't worry, I got your back.
Dave, get this thing off me.
I can't shake him.
- Uh-huh. On your tail.
- Come on, babe.
- Go under.
- You got it.
Okay, I got him. I got him.
Okay, you have another one
coming right up behind you.
- Dave, do a barrel roll.
- Oh, you got it, babe.
- Barrel roll.
- Come on.
Lock on it, Dave.
- I'm gonna get him.
- Come on.
Hurry, Mark.
- Yes! There it is.
- Okay, Mark.
- The coast is clear now. Hurry!
- Sure. Sure.
- Uh...
- Oh, shit.
Shit! No, no, no, no, no, no!
- Goddamn it.
- Mark, Mark, Mark, get it back up!
- Shit!
- Uh...
- It-it's not working.
- Flip it over.
- Flip it over!
- It-it won't turn over.
Like a damn turtle
on its back here.
Okay, I got an idea.
Come on, guys.
I'm running out of time.
Faith, get his number.
I don't think
this guy has a phone.
I mean, he must have
a phone. Everyone has a phone.
Oh, my God. Come on.
Tell him to flip the drone.
Come on, come on, come on.
What's he doing? Come on.
You can do it. Come on,
come on, come on, come on.
Just... just flip it over.
Just...
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on. I've got a better idea.
Why is he waiting?
- What's going on?
- Ugh!
Wait.
Wait, wait, uh, g-give him, uh,
an Amazon gift card
for a thousand bucks.
Hurry! Come on.
Yes! Oh, my God.
Come on, come on, come on.
All right,
now, now, now, now, now!
Move, move, move, move!
Flip over for me, baby.
Come on. Come on, yes!
Talk to me, Goose.
How we looking?
Under control, Pops.
Okay, which way?
Dad, I've never used
this before. Give me a sec.
Gotcha. Okay, the door is
right in front of you. Hurry!
Begin strike formation.
Five minutes to DHS target.
Guys, the bombers
are five minutes out.
You've got to hurry.
Uh...
Dave, Dave, uh,
I need some help here.
I got you, brother.
Don't worry, I got your back.
Okay. I got missile locked.
Firing.
- Damn! I'm out of missiles.
- I need some help.
Someone think of something fast.
- You got it.
- Bait and switch.
I'll be the decoy.
- You got this.
- Wait.
Wait, I-I got an idea.
Boom!
Holy crap! Badass.
Go off, Dave.
There should be
a staircase on the left,
20 feet ahead.
What staircase? Where? Where?
Go left at Han Solo.
Got it. Okay.
We're in business.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
Uh, I'm losing signal here.
Where's that drive?
I need that drone!
On its way.
I-I can't see shit.
Which way do I go?
I'm flying blind here.
You're in the server room.
Five aisles down, make a right.
Okay.
Will, there must be ten
right on top of you.
One penetrated the building.
No!
Dad, no, no!
Move, bitch! Get out the way!
Yes!
These things are everywhere!
Where are you?
- I'm in.
- Okay.
Looks like the Goliath
access point
is in a sealed room
off this section somewhere.
I just got to find it
on the map.
There it is!
Five aisles down, make a left.
Mark, how far are you?
I'll be honest, I don't know
if the drone's gonna
make it, guys.
The battery's dying.
It's a mess.
Uh, base commander,
two-minute warning
to DHS target.
Will, you got two minutes.
Goddamn. There it is. Goliath.
Where is that drone?
Mark, I need it now!
Sir. Sir, uh, I'm here.
Where are you?
Make a right. Hurry up.
- Yeah, baby.
- Incoming!
I got it.
Good job, Mark.
Shit. My damn
access card doesn't work.
Hey, Faith, rewind
the security footage.
- Try to find the code.
- How do I do that?
Go to "file"
and click "footage playback."
See if you can find someone
entering the server room.
I think I got it.
One-one-one-nine-eight-three.
Goliath security code accepted.
Yes. Yes.
Access granted.
All right, Goliath,
it's dinnertime.
Dad, the USB input
should be right on the server face.
One minute to impact, Will.
One minute.
No!
Come on, man, you got this.
Get up, Dad! Get up!
I love you guys.
Holy shit, it's working.
The cannibal code is uploading.
Checking
the data centers. Stand by.
Really did it. Dad, are you...
Are you seeing this?
Abort. Abort. Abort.
Roger that. That was close.
Oh, my God, they're aborting.
- They're aborting the mission.
- Yes.
- Will did it.
Dad, you did it.
Dear Faith and Dave...
Being a parent is hard.
If I don't tell you
this stuff now,
I might not be able
to tell you later.
Protecting my kids was the
most important part of my life.
But I held on too long.
I was afraid
to let you guys grow up.
Please forgive my trespasses.
I promised Mom
I'd keep you safe,
but you ended up saving me.
"Faith, Mark is the man
I hoped he would be for you.
He'll make a great father,
"and you're gonna make
a great mom."
"Dave, you took chances
to defend the rights
of people you may never meet,
and that's the true character
of a leader.
Thank you for showing me
the way back to what's right.
Continue the rebellion.
"Security and privacy should not
mean giving up our freedom."
You have all become
the leaders I hoped you would be,
and your mom would be so proud
of her children.
I know it's true
that if I make it through this
it'll be because of you guys.
Just remember,
I'm with you always.
I love you both.
Your dad.
- Secretary Crystal.
- Mr. Radford.
How may I help you?
Mr. Radford, tremendous work.
You've done your country
a great service.
I just got off
with the president.
He wants you to pioneer
a new data collecting protocol
that doesn't invade
people's personal privacy.
Hmm. Sorry, sir, but not for me.
I beg your pardon?
There's more important
things to do
than to worry about
what's in people's Amazon cart.
I don't understand.
I'm done watching us.
From now on,
I'm watching you guys.
But the president...
♪ If you want to do
your thing ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ Stay true
and don't you bend ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ We're all kings
and queens within ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ You got to lose
before you win ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ A great disaster ♪
♪ Distracts
from boredom ahead ♪
♪ Fire and brimstone ♪
♪ A warning of nothing
for men ♪
♪ Are you complicit? ♪
♪ Or will you be... ♪
Mark, Mark, can you hear me?
What? Who is that?
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ If you want to
do your thing ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ Stay true ♪
♪ And don't you ever bend ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ We are kings
and queens within ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ You got to lose ♪
♪ Before you win ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ We are kings
and queens within ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ You got to lose ♪
♪ Before you win ♪
♪ So keep your head up ♪
♪ Oh, keep your head up ♪
♪ Oh, keep your head up... ♪
♪ Keep your head up ♪
♪ Oh, keep your, keep your ♪
♪ Keep your ♪
♪ Keep your head up. ♪